<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Dietary</string>
    <string name="gallery_button">Gallery</string>
    <string name="rotate_button">Rotate</string>
    <string name="camera_supporting_text">Make sure all food is inside the circle</string>
    <string name="home_title">Home</string>
    <string name="report_title">Report</string>
    <string name="my_profile_title">My Profile</string>
    <string name="account_and_security_title">Account and Security</string>
    <string name="sign_out_title">Sign Out</string>
    <string name="age_label">Age</string>
    <string name="weight_label">Weight</string>
    <string name="height_label">Height</string>
    <string name="gender_label">Gender</string>
    <string name="save">Save</string>
    <string-array name="gender">
        <item>Male</item>
        <item>Female</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="food_scanner_title">Food Scanner</string>
    <string name="camera_permission_message">Food scanner isn\'t available because you denied camera access. You can enable it in settings.</string>
    <string name="yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="no_thanks">No, thanks</string>
    <string name="camera_access_dialog_message">Camera access is needed for the food scanner. Do you want to grant permission?</string>
    <string name="sign_in_with_google">Sign in with Google</string>
    <string name="or">Or</string>
    <string name="email_address_placeholder">What\'s your email address?</string>
    <string name="email_address_label">Email Address</string>
    <string name="email_address_error_text">Please enter a valid email address</string>
    <string name="supporting_text_required">*required</string>
    <string name="password_placeholder">What\'s your password?</string>
    <string name="old_password_placeholder">What\'s your old password?</string>
    <string name="api_url_placeholder">Enter API URL</string>
    <string name="new_password_placeholder">Create your new password</string>
    <string name="password_error_text">Password must be at least 8 characters long and include a mix of lowercase, uppercase, numbers, special characters, and no spaces</string>
    <string name="password_label">Password</string>
    <string name="welcome_back">Welcome back!</string>
    <string name="you_ve_been_missed">You\'ve been missed 🤗</string>
    <string name="sign_in">Sign In</string>
    <string name="don_t_have_an_account">Don\'t have an account?</string>
    <string name="sign_up_here">Sign up here</string>
    <string name="forgot_password">Forgot Password?</string>
    <string name="join_us_today">🌟 Join Us! 🌟</string>
    <string name="confirmation_password_placeholder">Re-enter your password</string>
    <string name="confirmation_password_error_text">Please confirm your password correctly</string>
    <string name="sign_up">Sign Up</string>
    <string name="have_an_account">Have an account?</string>
    <string name="sign_in_here">Sign in here</string>
    <string name="reset_password">Reset Password!</string>
    <string name="reset_password_message">Forgot your password? No worries,\nwe\'ll send you reset instructions</string>
    <string name="new_password_message">Enter your new password</string>
    <string name="add_my_profile_label">Let\'s make\nhealthy eating\nfun and easy 🥗💪</string>
    <string name="username_placeholder">Create your username</string>
    <string name="username_label">Username</string>
    <string name="username_error_text">Please enter a username between 6 and 20 characters without spaces or special characters like @, $, etc.</string>
    <string name="age_placeholder">What\'s your age?</string>
    <string name="age_error_text">You must be at least 18 years old</string>
    <string name="weight_placeholder">What\'s your weight?</string>
    <string name="weight_error_text">Weight must be a number greater than 0</string>
    <string name="height_placeholder">What\'s your height?</string>
    <string name="height_error_text">Height must be a number greater than 0</string>
    <string name="waist_error_text">Waist circumference must be a number greater than 0</string>
    <string name="trailing_text_kg">kg</string>
    <string name="trailing_text_cm">cm</string>
    <string name="goal_label">Goal</string>
    <string name="target_weight_label">Target Weight</string>
    <string name="target_weight_placeholder">What\'s your target weight?</string>
    <string name="target_weight_error_text">Target weight must be a number greater than 0</string>
    <string name="activity_level_label">Activity Level</string>
    <string name="build_profile">Build Profile</string>
    <string name="confirmation_password_label">Confirm Password</string>
    <string name="verify_email">Verify Email</string>
    <string name="terms_of_use_label_button">By clicking get started or sign in, you agree to the</string>
    <string name="terms_of_use">Terms of Use</string>
    <string name="welcome_to">Welcome to</string>
    <string name="dietary">" Dietary!"</string>
    <string name="your_diet_s_best_ally">" Your diet\'s best friend 🌟"</string>
    <string name="landing_message">Check out your Food Diary:\nTrack your meals! 🥘🍱</string>
    <string name="get_started">Get Started</string>
    <string name="failed_to_took_picture">Failed to take picture</string>
    <string-array name="goal">
        <item>Weight Loss</item>
        <item>Maintain current weight</item>
        <item>Weight Gain</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="activity_level">
        <item>Sedentary</item>
        <item>Low Active</item>
        <item>Active</item>
        <item>Very Active</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="activity_description">
        <item>Daily activities require minimal effort like resting, desk work, or driving.</item>
        <item>Daily activities require some effort like standing, housework, or light exercise.</item>
        <item>Daily activities require moderate effort like standing, physical work, or regular light exercise.</item>
        <item>Daily activities require intense physical effort like construction work or heavy regular exercise.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="retry">Retry</string>
    <string name="searchbar_hint">Find your food diary!</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="ok">OK</string>
    <string name="diary_display">Check out your Food Diary:\nTrack your meals! 🥘🍱</string>
    <string name="empty_content_label">No food diary entries yet</string>
    <string name="empty_content_search">The food you\'re looking for can\'t be found</string>
    <string name="cm">%1$s cm</string>
    <string name="year">%1$s years</string>
    <string name="kg">%1$s kg</string>
    <string name="title">Title</string>
    <string name="title_error_text">Title cannot be empty</string>
    <string name="title_placeholder">Enter food diary title</string>
    <string name="calories">Calories</string>
    <string name="kcal">%1$s kcal</string>
    <string name="fat">Fats</string>
    <string name="g">%1$s g</string>
    <string name="protein">Proteins</string>
    <string name="carbohydrates">Carbohydrates</string>
    <string name="sugar">Sugar</string>
    <string name="feedback">Feedback</string>
    <string name="total_calories">Total Food Calories</string>
    <string name="category_label">Category</string>
    <string name="question">Question</string>
    <string-array name="food_diary_category">
        <item>Breakfast</item>
        <item>Lunch</item>
        <item>Dinner</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="appwidget_text">Dietary</string>
    <string name="api_url_label">API URL</string>
    <string name="api_url_error_text">URL must be in https format</string>
    <string name="serving_unit">✧ %1$s (100 g)</string>
    <string name="food_nutrition_label">Nutrition</string>
    <string name="continue_button">Continue</string>
    <string name="re_add">Re-add</string>
    <string name="wheel_max_label">%1$s/\nMax %2$s</string>
    <string name="waist_circumference_placeholder">Enter your waist circumference</string>
    <string name="waist_circumference_label">Waist Circumference</string>
    <string name="food_diary">Food Diary</string>
    <string name="progress">✦ Progress</string>
    <string name="your_nutrition_today">✦ Your Nutrition Today</string>
    <string name="dev_mode_notification">Dev Mode Notification</string>
    <string name="dev_mode_notif_title">Dev Mode</string>
    <string name="open_dev_mode_menu">Open dev mode menu</string>
    <string name="dev_mode_dismiss_message">Grant notification permissions through your Android settings</string>
    <string name="dev_mode_body">To access the dev mode menu, please grant notification access</string>
    <string name="allow">Allow</string>
    <string name="reset">Reset</string>
    <string name="weight_legend">Weight (kg)</string>
    <string name="waist_circumeference_legend">Waist Circumference (cm)</string>
    <string name="calorie_legend">Calories (kcal)</string>
    <string name="carbo_legend">Carbohydrates (g)</string>
    <string name="nutrition">✦ Nutrition</string>
    <string name="protein_legend">Proteins (g)</string>
    <string name="fat_legend">Fats (g)</string>
    <string name="change_email">Change Email</string>
    <string name="change_password">Change Password</string>
    <string name="renew">Update</string>
    <string name="total_carbohydrates">Total Food Carbohydrates</string>
    <string name="total_protein">Total Food Proteins</string>
    <string name="total_fat">Total Food Fats</string>
    <string name="didnt_receive">Didn\'t receive it?</string>
    <string name="resend">Resend %1$s</string>
    <string name="your_food_diaries">✦ Your Food Diaries</string>
    <string name="progress_max_label">Max %1$s</string>
    <string name="empty_data">No data to display</string>
    <string name="verify_code_label">"Enter the 6-digit code sent to "</string>
    <string name="successfully_signed_up">You successfully signed up</string>
    <string name="success">Success</string>
    <string name="check_your_mailbox">Check your email inbox</string>
    <string name="successfully_changed_email_address">Successfully changed email address</string>
    <string name="successfully_changed_password">Successfully changed password</string>
    <string name="day">Day</string>
    <string name="week">Week</string>
    <string name="weekly">Weekly</string>
    <string name="monthly">Monthly</string>
    <string name="weight_and_waist_line_chart_title">Weight and Waist Circumference</string>
    <string name="calories_and_carbohydrates_line_chart_title">Calories and Carbohydrates</string>
    <string name="proteins_and_fats_line_chart_title">Proteins and Fats</string>
    <string name="food_diary_is_not_found">Food diary is not found</string>
    <string name="food_introduction_title"><![CDATA[Discover Your Perfect Balance: Flavorful & Healthy Choices Await]]></string>
    <string name="take_picture_introduction_title">Snap It to Know It: Your Food\'s Nutritional Secrets Revealed</string>
    <string name="report_introduction_title">See Your Progress, Own Your Health: Track Your Journey to a Healthier You!</string>
    <string name="food_introduction_description">Craving a delicious meal that won\'t derail your health goals? Look no further! Our app is your personalized guide to navigating the world of food, where taste and nutrition go hand in hand.</string>
    <string name="take_picture_introduction_description">Snap a pic and we\'ll break down the nutrients, calories, and everything else you need to know to keep your health goals on track!</string>
    <string name="report_introduction_description">You\'ve logged your meals, now let\'s visualize your progress! Track your nutrition, weight, and waistline changes over time to make informed choices and celebrate your achievements!</string>
    <string name="terms_of_use_description">
1. API License, Use and Restrictions\nThe FatSecret Platform API is owned by FatSecret. Subject to the restrictions described in these Terms of Use, FatSecret grants you a non-exclusive, revocable, nonsublicensable, nontransferable license to download and use the FatSecret Platform API to develop an application (your \"Application\") through which you may access FatSecret and third party data, content, information and other materials (\"Content\").
These Terms of Use define the legal use of the FatSecret Platform API, all updates, revisions, substitutions, and any copies of the FatSecret Platform API made by or for you. All rights not expressly granted to you are reserved by FatSecret.\n
1.1 Your license to the FatSecret Platform API under these Terms of Use continues until it is terminated by either party. You may terminate the license by discontinuing use of all or any of the FatSecret Platform API. FatSecret may terminate the license at any time for any reason. Your license terminates automatically if (i) you violate any term of these Terms of Use, (ii) FatSecret sends a written notice of termination to you, or (iii) FatSecret ceases providing you access to the FatSecret Platform API.\n
1.2 Your Application must be generally accessible to users. You may require users to log in to your Application but you must not (unless you have entered into a separate agreement with FatSecret or obtained FatSecret\'s written permission) operate only behind a firewall or only on an internal network (except during the development and testing phase).\n
1.3 You must clearly attribute in every place that Content is provided or displayed through your Application (such as a web page or application screen), that FatSecret is the source of such Content and comply with the FatSecret Platform API Attribution Policy. You may not remove any copyright, trademark or other proprietary rights notices contained in or on the Content. You understand and agree that you must retain the attribution links for the Content regardless of whether you continue using the FatSecret Platform API for any reason.\n
1.4 Your Application may make calls or data retrieval requests (\"Calls\") at any time that the FatSecret Platform API is available. You understand that there is a rate limit per Application utilizing the FatSecret Platform API and you agree to comply with that rate limit at all times. The amount of the rate limit is 5,000 calls per day and such amount may change from time to time our sole and absolute discretion. Any limit imposed on the number of Calls allowed per day per Key will expire at the close of each day, with any unused requests not being carried over. Increases in any limit imposed can be sought by contacting us. You understand and agree that programmatic methods intended to subvert rate limiting are considered a violation of these Terms of Use.\n
1.5 You may not continue to use and must immediately remove or replace (by re-requesting) any Content in your possession or under your control not explicitly identified as being storable indefinitely within 24 hours after the time at which you obtained the Content, or such other time as FatSecret may specify to you from time to time. You may store and use indefinitely Content that is explicitly identified as being storable indefinitely provided, however, that you may not continue to use, and must immediately remove or replace (by re-requesting) any Content in your possession or under your control if FatSecret ceases to explicitly identify the Content as being storable indefinitely; or upon any termination of the license for any reason.\n
1.6 If your Application uses the FatSecret Platform API to obtain and display Content in conjunction with your content for use by other users, you must:\n
i. display to the users of your Applications the link to these Terms of Use;\n
ii. explicitly state in your Applications terms of use that, by using your software application or website, your users are agreeing to be bound by these Terms of Use; and\n
iii. protect the privacy and legal rights of those users.\n
1.7 You must not:\n
i. copy, rent, lease, sell, transfer, assign, sublicense, disassemble, reverse engineer or decompile (except to the limited extent expressly authorized by law), modify or alter any part of the FatSecret Platform API, without FatSecret\'s prior written consent;\n
ii. use the FatSecret Platform API in any manner or for any purpose that violates any law or regulation, any right of any person, including but not limited to intellectual property rights, rights of privacy, or rights of personality, or in any manner inconsistent with the FatSecret Terms &amp; Conditions or these Terms of Use. You understand that all trademarks, copyright and other forms of intellectual property are property of their respective owners;\n
iii. use the FatSecret Platform API to provide diet, nutrition or health advice, guidance or diagnosis and make clear that any information generated using the FatSecret Platform API should not be interpreted as a substitute for medical physician consultation, evaluation, or treatment. You understand that the FatSecret Platform API is not designed for such purposes and that its failure in such cases could lead to personal injury or damage for which FatSecret is not responsible; or\n
iv. use the FatSecret Platform API in a manner that exceeds reasonable request volume, constitutes excessive or abusive usage (including using any robot, spider, site search/retrieval, or other automated application or device to retrieve or index any portion of the Content), or otherwise fails to comply with any part of the FatSecret Platform API documentation, as determined by FatSecret in our absolute discretion.\n
You understand and agree to provide us with access to your Applications that uses the FatSecret Platform API as reasonably requested by us to verify your compliance with these Terms of Use. You agree that we may crawl or otherwise monitor these Applications and you agree not to block or interfere with such efforts by FatSecret in any way.\n\n
2. Support\n
These Terms of Use do not entitle you to any support for the FatSecret Platform API or your Applications, unless you make separate arrangements with FatSecret. FatSecret may elect to provide you with support or modifications for the FatSecret Platform API in our absolute discretion, and may terminate such Support at any time without notice to you. FatSecret may change, suspend, or discontinue any aspect of the FatSecret Platform API at any time, including their availability.\n\n
3. Application Development, Promotion &amp; Advertising\n
You understand and agree that FatSecret may independently create applications, content and other products or services that may be similar to or competitive with your Applications, and nothing in these Terms of Use will be construed as restricting or preventing FatSecret from creating and fully exploiting such applications, content and other items, without any obligation to you.
We welcome the provision of feedback in relation to the FatSecret Platform API and if you elect to provide us with any feedback you understand and agree to assign all right, title and interest in such feedback to us and that we are entitled to use, implement and exploit any such feedback in any manner without restriction, and without any obligation of confidentiality, attribution or compensation.You may promote your Applications, including talking to traditional and online media and your users about your Application, so long as you do truthfully and without implying that your Application is created or endorsed by FatSecret.
FatSecret reserves the right to include advertising in or associated with any images provided to you through the FatSecret Platform API. If FatSecret decides to include advertising, such decision will be disclosed to you prior to its effect.\n\n
4. Disclaimer\n
FatSecret does not represent or warrant that the FatSecret Platform API is free of inaccuracies, errors, bugs or interruptions, or are reliable, accurate or complete. In particular, product information from the FatSecret Platform API may vary from the information on products in distribution, and ingredients, formulations and packaging may change so you should refer to the nutrition information on a product package for the most accurate information.
The FatSecret Platform API is provided \"as is\" with no warranty, express or implied, of any kind and FatSecret expressly disclaims any and all warranties and conditions, including but not limited to, any implied warranty of merchantability, accuracy, results of use, fitness for a particular purpose, availability, security, title and non-infringement of third-party rights.
Your use of the FatSecret Platform API is at your own discretion and risk and you will be solely responsible for any damage that results from their use.\n\n
5. Limitation of Liability\n
FatSecret shall not, under any circumstances, be liable to you or any third party for any indirect, consequential, exemplary, incidental, special or punitive damages, including for loss of profits, lost or corrupted data, computer malfunction or business interruption, arising out of or in connection with your use of the FatSecret Platform API, even if FatSecret has been advised of the possibility of such damages. FatSecret disclaims all liability of any kind for any third party Content.\n\n
6. Indemnity\n
To the maximum extent permitted by applicable law, you agree to indemnify and hold FatSecret, its subsidiaries, and affiliates, and their respective officers, agents, partners and employees, harmless from any loss, liability, claim, or demand, including reasonable attorneys\' fees, made by any third party due to or arising out of or in connection with your use of the FatSecret Platform API. FatSecret shall use good faith efforts to provide you with written notice of such claim or demand.\n\n
7. General\n
7.1 These Terms of Use constitute the entire agreement between you and FatSecret regarding the use of the FatSecret Platform API.\n
7.2 Notwithstanding any provision to the contrary, for all purposes of these Terms of Use, you and FatSecret shall be and act independently and not as partner, joint venturer, agent, employee or employer of the other. You shall not have any authority to assume or create any obligation for or on behalf of FatSecret, express or implied, and you shall not attempt to bind FatSecret to any contract.\n
7.3 The failure of FatSecret to exercise or enforce any right or provision of these Terms of Use shall not operate as a waiver of such right or provision.\n
7.4 If any provision of these Terms of Use is unlawful, void or unenforceable, that provision is deemed severable from these Terms of Use and does not affect the validity and enforceability of any remaining provisions.\n
7.5 These Terms of Use and any dispute about or involving the FatSecret Platform API shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of the State of Victoria, Australia, without regard to conflict of law provisions. You agree that any action at law or in equity arising out of or relating to your use of the FatSecret Platform API or these Terms of Use shall be filed only in the state or federal courts located in Victoria, Australia and you hereby consent and submit to the personal jurisdiction of such courts for the purposes of litigating any such action, provided that the foregoing shall not prevent FatSecret from seeking injunctive relief in a court of competent jurisdiction.</string>
    <string name="skip">Skip</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy">Effective Date: May 28, 2024\n\nWelcome to Dietary! Your privacy is important to us. This Privacy Policy explains how we collect, use, disclose, and safeguard your information when you use our mobile application (the "App"). Please read this policy carefully to understand our views and practices regarding your personal data and how we will treat it.\n\n1. Information We Collect\nWe collect and process the following personal information:\nAge: Your age, which must be at least 18 years old to use our app.\nWeight: Your weight in kilograms or pounds.\nHeight: Your height in centimeters or inches.\nGender: Your gender identification.\nGoal: Your fitness or health goals.\nWeight Target: Your target weight.\nActivity Level: Your level of physical activity (e.g., sedentary, active).\nWaist Circumference: The measurement of your waist in centimeters or inches.\nActive Burned Calories: The number of calories burned during physical activities.\n\n2. How We Use Your Information\nWe use the information we collect in the following ways:\nPersonalization: To tailor the app experience to your individual health and fitness goals.\nAnalytics: To understand how our app is used and to improve its functionality and user experience.\nSupport: To provide customer support and respond to your inquiries.\n\n3. Data Storage and Security\nWe implement appropriate technical and organizational measures to protect your personal information against accidental or unlawful destruction, loss, alteration, unauthorized disclosure, or access. However, please note that no method of transmission over the internet or method of electronic storage is 100% secure.\n\n4. Sharing Your Information\nWe do not share your personal information with third parties except as described in this policy or as required by law. We may share your data with:\nService Providers: Third-party vendors who perform services on our behalf, such as hosting and data analytics.\nLegal Obligations: If required to do so by law or in response to valid requests by public authorities (e.g., a court or a government agency).\n\n5. Data Retention\nWe will retain your personal information only for as long as is necessary for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy. We will retain and use your information to the extent necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.\n\n6. Your Data Protection Rights\nDepending on your location, you may have the following rights regarding your personal data:\nAccess: The right to access and obtain a copy of your personal data.\nRectification: The right to correct any inaccurate or incomplete personal data.\nErasure: The right to request the deletion of your personal data under certain conditions.\nRestriction: The right to restrict the processing of your personal data under certain conditions.\nObjection: The right to object to our processing of your personal data.\nData Portability: The right to receive your personal data in a structured, commonly used, and machine-readable format.\n\n7. Changes to This Privacy Policy\nWe may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page. You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes.\n\n8. Contact Us\nIf you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at:\n\nEmail: privacy@dietary.cloud\nBy using our app, you acknowledge that you have read and understood this Privacy Policy. Thank you for choosing Dietary!
    </string>
    <string name="and">" and"</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_title">" Privacy Policy"</string>
    <string name="save_food_diary">save food diary</string>
    <string name="take_a_picture">take a picture</string>
    <string name="list_of_foods">list of foods</string>
</resources>